Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
- Box: 65, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Item 9: Facts, Publication (Box 65, Folder 24)
    Notes: to help you stay safe in the receiving, warehouse and shipping division
  - Item 10: Safety Program - 1959, Publication (Box 65, Folder 24)
- Box: 65, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Steps in Planned Management Development, Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Scheduling and Charting the Learning Period, 1951; Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
    Notes: Training Exchange
  - Item 3: Managerial Position Description, 1951; Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Training Evaluation Chart in Use at Mishawaka, 1950; Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Reading List on Supervisory Training, 1952; Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: Steps in Planned Management Development, Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Item 7: Techniques For Executive Development, Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Item 8: How Naugatuck Footwear Gets Down to Brass Tacks In Talks With Employes, 1955; Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
    Notes: Employe Information Community Relations
  - Item 9: Making Your Meetings Pay Off: Principles of Conference Leadership, 1951; Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Item 10: Industrial Exposition Exhibit Photos, Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Item 11: Round-Up: "U.S." Plant Activities, 1955; Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
    Notes: Employee Information Community Relations
  - Item 12: Plants Stress Competition In Employe Publications, 1957; Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Item 13: Detroit, Providence Sponsor Junior Achievement Groups, 1953; Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Item 14: Hide Tailors, Inc. Distribution of Bonus As of 5-6-53, 1953; Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Item 15: Accountants Certificate, 1953; Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
    Author: F.J. Whitsell, I.J. Kraemer
  - Item 16: Tips for Supervisory Training, 1951; Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
    Author: R.R. Crow
    Notes: To: Training Directors
  - Item 17: Supervisor Safety Training, Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
    Notes: Four and One Half Hour Training Course in Three Sessions
  - Item 18: The Unitedf States Rubber Company Basic Management Training Leading to First Line Supervision in the Mill Room, Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Item 19: Secretarial Training Program, 1951; Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Item 20: Use of Photographs in Instruction, 1951; Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Item 21: Secretarial Training Program, Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
- Box: 65, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Security For You, Publication (Box 65, Folder 26)
    Notes: Your Plan of Group Insurance
  - Item 2: Information Concerning A Plan of Employees Cooperative Group Life and Group Accident and Sickness Insurance, Publication (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Job Classification: Production and Maintenance Jobs, Publication (Box 65, Folder 26)
    Notes: Cooperative Wage Study Manual Covering Midvale Plant and U.S. And Lark Mine
- Box: 65, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Career Development and Training Guide, 1965; Publication (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Training: Responsibility for Work Improvement, 1965; Publication (Box 65, Folder 27)
- Box: 66, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Safety Rules For Arc Welding, 1950; Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: General Safety and Plant Conduct, 1954; Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
    Notes: Rules and Regulations
  - Item 3: Crane Safety Rules, 1958; Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Departmental Safety Rules, Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Departmental Safety Rules, Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
    Notes: Open Hearth Metallurgical masonry
  - Item 6: Plant Safety Rules, Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Safety Rules for Office Employees, 1955; Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: General Safety Rules for Slab and Plate Personnel, Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Safety Rules for Arc Welding, 1957; Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Who Can Make National Tube Company The Safest Steel Company on Earth?, 1951; Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Benefits To Be Derived From Accident Investigation, 1962; Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
    Author: R.T. Ives
    Notes: Technical Paper: Business Administration and Economics
  - Item 12: Safety In Mining, 1959; Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
    Author: Woods G. Talman
    Notes: Technical Paper: Mining and Geology
  - Item 13: Gas Safety Manual, 1956; Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
    Notes: Detection, Protection and Rescue
  - Item 14: Safety Program, 1964; Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Box: 66, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Explosion Hazard Manual, 1955; Publication (Box 66, Folder 2)
    Notes: Utility Section
  - Item 2: Explosion Hazards Manual, 1958; Publication (Box 66, Folder 2)
    Notes: Open Hearth Section
- Box: 66, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Explosion Hazards Manual, 1958; Publication (Box 66, Folder 3)
    Notes: Coke and Chemical Products Section
  - Item 2: Explosion Hazards Manual, 1958; Publication (Box 66, Folder 3)
    Notes: Rolling Mills Section
- Box: 66, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: You and Your Company, Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Employe Manual of Information and Guidance, 1953; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: The 3 C's of Safety, 1951; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Group Insurance Plan for Eligible Salaried Employees, 1975; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Program of Insurance Benefits For Employees of United States Steel Corporation and Subsidiary Companies, 1967; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Notes: Hourly Paid Employees
  - Item 6: Group Insurance Plan for Eligible Salaried Employees, 1968; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Program of Insurance Benefits for Employees of United States Steel Corporation and Subsidiary Companies, 1967; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Insurance Benefits Plan For Participating Employees of United States Steel Corporation and Subsidiary Companies: Hourly Paid Employees, 1954; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Notes: Established Pursuant to Agreement with United Steelworkers of America
  - Item 9: Insurance Benefits Plan for Participating Employees of Untied States Steel Corporation And Subsidiary Companies, 1952; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Insurance Benefits Plan for Participating Employees of Untied States Steel Corporation And Subsidiary Companies, 1951; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Group Insurance Plan For Eligible Salaried Employees, 1953; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Training Film Catalog, 1953; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Training Films, Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Notes: Motion Pictures & Sound Slides
  - Item 14: Basic Facts About U.S. Steel, 1969; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Announcement of Company Disablilty Benefits Plan For Employees of United States Steel Corporation And Its Subsidiaries, 1950; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Announcement of Company Voluntary Plan of Unemployment Compensation Disability Benefits For Employees of United States Steel Corporation Subsidiaries, 1952; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Announcement of Company Temporary Disablility Benefits Plan For Employees of United States Steel Corporation and Its Subsidiaries, 1950; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Program of Advance Technical Study, Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Notes: Voluntary Evening Classes for United States Steel Employees: Fall Semester - 1961
  - Item 19: A Guide for New Employees, Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Notes: Ore Mines and Quarries
  - Item 20: Your Information Manual, Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Notes: Fairless Works
  - Item 21: Information About Forthcoming Negotiations, 1959; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: An Appraisal of Collective Bargaining in a Free Society, 1967; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Author: R. Conrad Cooper
  - Item 23: The National Interest in Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: You and United Stainless Steel, Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: Labor Relations In U.S. Steel, 1955; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Author: John A. Stephens
  - Item 26: Mature Collective Bargaining- Prospects and Problems, 1950; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 27: Program of Insurance Benefits For Employees of United States Steel Corporation and Subsidiary Companies: Hourly-Paid Employes, 1956; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 28: Program of Hospital And Medical Benefits Supplementing Medicare, 1969; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Notes: Provided by Blue Cross and Blue Shield For Eligible Pensioners of United States Steel Corporation And Subsidiary Companies
  - Item 29: Program of Hospital and Physicians' Services Benefits For Eligible Pensioners And Surviving Spouses Not Eligible for Medicare, 1975; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 30: Program of Hospital and Physicians' Services Benefits for Eligible Pensioners And Surviving Spouses not Eligible for Medicare, 1974; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Item 31: Program of Hospital and Physicians' Services Benefits for Eligible Pensioners And Surviving Spouses not Eligible for Medicare, 1974; Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Box: 66, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Safety Guide Pertaining To Physical Conditions Based on "General Requirements For Safety Pertaining To Physical Conditions", 1954; Publication (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Explosion Hazards Manual, 1963; Publication (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Box: 66, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Summary Plan Description of United States Steel 1976 Non-Contributory Pension Rules, Publication (Box 66, Folder 6)
    Notes: part II-H(E) Pension Rules
- Box: 66, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Summary Plan Description of United States Steel 1976 Non-Contributory Pension Rules, Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
    Notes: Part II-H(E) Pension Rules
  - Item 2: Summary Plan Description of United States Steel 1976 Contributory Pension Rules, Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
    Notes: Part IV-F Pension Rules
  - Item 3: United States Steel 1969 Non-Contributory Pension Rules Applicable to Employees Subject to the Social Security Act and Financial Provisions for Non-Contributory Pensions, Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
    Notes: Part II-F Pension Rules; Part III Pension Rules
  - Item 4: 1969 Contributory Pension Rules, Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
    Notes: Part IV-C Pension Rules
  - Item 5: United States Steel 1960 Non-Contributory Pension Rules, Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
    Notes: Part IIC Pension Rules
  - Item 6: 1965 Contributory Pension Rules of United States Steel Contributory Pension Plan, Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
    Notes: Part IV-B Pension Rules
  - Item 7: United States Steel 1966 Non-Contributory Pension Rules, Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
    Notes: Part II-E Pension Rules
  - Item 8: Employee Suggestion Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Employee Suggestion Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Program of Hospital and Medical Benefits Supplementing Medicare, 1966; Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
    Notes: Provided by Blue Cross and Blue Shield
  - Item 11: Major Medical Expense Insurance For Eligible Pensioners, 1966; Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Provided Under Program of Insurance Benefits for Designated Employees of the United States Steel Corporation, 1962; Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Supplemental Unemployment Benefits, Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Another Look At Wage Inflation, 1959; Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
    Author: Robert C. Tyson
  - Item 15: Your Business and Mine, Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
    Author: Benjamin F. Fairless
  - Item 16: Guidelines and the National Interest, 1962; Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
    Author: Heath Larry
  - Item 17: United States Steel Corporation 1954 Non-Contributory Pension Rules and Financial Provisions for Non-Contributory Pensions, Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Man's Search for Security, 1949; Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: Pension Rules, 1950; Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: Transfer & Relocation of Management Employees, 1975; Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Item 21: Employee Suggestion Plan, 1962; Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Item 22: Employee Suggestion Plan, 1963; Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Item 23: Job Opportunities Employee Handbook, 1962; Publication (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Box: 66, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: No. 155 Assembly Line Methods Speed U.S. Steel Mail, Publication (Box 66, Folder 8)
    Author: David W. Fleeger
    Notes: A Technical Paper
  - Item 2: Uniform Job Classification of Wage Incentive Development, 1951; Publication (Box 66, Folder 8)
    Author: J.D. McCall
  - Item 3: Today's Thinking on Tomorrow's Managing, 1958; Publication (Box 66, Folder 8)
    Author: Richard C. Anderson
    Notes: Technical Paper: Business Administration and Economics Volume VI, No. 9
  - Item 4: The Steel Industry Wage Rate Inequity Program, 1954; Publication (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: The Company Five-Year Offer, 1956; Publication (Box 66, Folder 8)
    Author: C.F. Hood
  - Item 6: Learning To Work Together, 1955; Publication (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Steel Collective Bargaining in the '60s, 1961; Publication (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: The Significance of the 1962 Negotiations, Publication (Box 66, Folder 8)
    Author: R. Heath Larry
  - Item 9: Your Information Manual, Publication (Box 66, Folder 8)
    Notes: Homestead District Works
  - Item 10: The Unted States Steel Corporation Versus Labor: The Early Years, 1960; Publication (Box 66, Folder 8)
    Author: John A. Garraty
    Notes: Reprint Series No. 24
  - Item 11: A Management Guide to Communication, Publication (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Practical Problems in Communications, 1961; Publication (Box 66, Folder 8)
    Author: Edgar B. Speer
    Notes: Technical Paper: Business Administration and Economics Volume VIII, Number 52
  - Item 13: Collective Bargaining At The Crossroads, 1967; Publication (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Box: 66, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Report on Insurance and Pensions By Joint Committee on Insurance and Pensions of United Steelworkers of America and United Steel Corporation, 1954; Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    Notes: Volume I: Insurance and Pension Programs of United States Steel Corporation
  - Item 2: Report on Insurance and Pensions By Joint Committee on Insurance and Pensions of United Steelworkers of America and United States Steel Corporation, 1954; Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    Notes: Volume II: Insurance and Pension Programs of Forty Companies
  - Item 3: Principles of Accident Prevention in United States Steel, 1965; Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    Notes: Workbook
  - Item 4: Safety in the Wood Shop, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Box: 66, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Principles of Accident Prevention, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Procedure Manual, 1960; Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    Notes: University Advanced Management Program
  - Item 3: Management Training in Compensation, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: USS Newsletter, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: U.S. Steel News, 1970; Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    Notes: Volume 35, Number 4
  - Item 6: General Management Development, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Box: 66, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Plant Protection, 1951; Publication (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Box: 66, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Plant Protection, 1951; Publication (Box 66, Folder 12)